Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Campaign for United States Congress, 1966; V.
  - Election results, 7.
    Election results from both the Primary and the General Election are here. Also included is a report written about the unsuccessful Thornburgh campaign: "The Broken Spoon: a study in failure" by Jeffrey A. Ernico, a Pitt student and campaign volunteer. The title refers to the photograph widely used in Thornburgh campaign literature and billboards of Thornburgh standing next to a giant wooden spoon with the slogan "Dick Thornburgh will stir things up in Congress."
    - Primary Election Results, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - General Election Results, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - "The Broken Spoon: A Study in Failure," by Jeffrey A. Ernico, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Campaign finances, 8.
    The bulk of the materials here relates to the campaign budget and contributions and is arranged chronologically.
    - Thornburgh for Congress Committee: Financial Matters (annotated), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Contributions: Alphabetical Copies of Letters, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Lists of Contributors from Various Organizations (annotated), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Form Letters Regarding Contributions, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Campaign Budget, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 9.
    Correspondence in these folders, arranged chronologically, covers the campaign effort. The correspondence is separated as follows: pre-primary, post-primary, pre-election and post-election. Correspondence is to and from voters, peers, co-workers, and constituents.
    - 1966 GOP Candidates and Ward Chairmen Letters (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Thornburgh's Campaign Correspondence, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 2-5)
    - Correspondence from Voters, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Post Election Lists for Thank You Letters, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Post Election Thank You Letters, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)